[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet featured in Star Wars was renamed Imperial Center?", "correct_answer": "Coruscant", "incorrect_answers": ["Jabiim", "Kashyyyk", "Byss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of the actress who played the main character on Maude?", "correct_answer": "Bea", "incorrect_answers": ["Amy", "Liz", "Pat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fake product is Rapunzel revealed to wear in the movie Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "Fake hair", "incorrect_answers": ["Fake eyelashes", "Color contacts", "Fake nails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these weapons is a US Marine infantry  weapon, scheduled for widespread use in starting 2008?", "correct_answer": "SMAW-NE", "incorrect_answers": ["Stryker", "M-17A2 rifle", "Javelin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the deepest spot in the oceans?", "correct_answer": "Mariana Trench", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuril-Kamchatka Trench", "Philippine Trench", "Tonga Trench"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus is largest when it is at which phase?", "correct_answer": "Crescent", "incorrect_answers": ["Half", "Full", "Gibbous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Jim Careys characters last name in Liar Liar?", "correct_answer": "Reede", "incorrect_answers": ["Holmes", "Barnanby", "Scholand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The great 1939 movie Juarez was the story of the rise of Democracy in Mexico and the overthrow of the Maximillan rule. Who played Juarez in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Paul Muni", "incorrect_answers": ["John Garfield", "Donald Crisp", "Brian Aherne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Conversation, Harry Cauls friend, Stan, is played by an actor who only made five feature films. Three of them were Oscar-nominated. Who was this actor and former Meryl Streep fiance?", "correct_answer": "John Cazale", "incorrect_answers": ["John Garfield", "William Smithee", "William Garfield"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed rebellious slave Spartacus in Stanley Kubricks 1960 historical movie Spartacus?", "correct_answer": "Kirk Douglas", "incorrect_answers": ["Laurence Olivier", "Omar Sharif", "Tony Curtis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In about how many years does the planet Saturn finish one revolution around the Sun?", "correct_answer": "29 1/2 years", "incorrect_answers": ["30 years", "29 years", "28 1/2 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Hawaiian language this word means woman.", "correct_answer": "wahine (wah-hee-knee)", "incorrect_answers": ["hoaloha (hoe-ah-low-hah)", "kane (kah-nay)", "makuahine (maa-koo-ah-hee-knee)"]}]